[Music]
And definitely my journey should be completed with you
ICICI Prudential
ICICI Prus Sukh Samriddhi Jain
Adhitabyamanshi a regular guaranteed income
policy with a loan on maturity Sam
Rakampand Pawan Kumar got a
guaranteed income no source
prosperity income no option you have many
benefits which you get 10 years from now
premium payment term is completed
featured use karisho win we
liked you date income Akshay
's live you have no wars income definitely neither
income our money saving wallet value deposit the amount
deposited today the amount is increasing
then I want to keep the policy term in your
feet use karisho leave the complete
policy
[Music]